xmind.net 2018-03-28

# Privacy Policy - XMind: The Most Popular Mind Mapping Software on The Planet.

The privacy policy of XMind, Ltd. covers the collection and use of personal data. This information may be collected any time you have interactive contact with us, such as when you buy our products and services, interact with our websites and online forums, or communicate with our sales or technical support staff. Your privacy is important to us. Our practices in handling your personal information are described in more detail below.

### PERSONAL INFORMATION

XMind, Ltd. collects your personal information to provide you with our products and services in the most convenient and user-friendly way. 

  * Account-Related Activity. Certain products and services offered through our website (collectively, including all content and technology available through the XMind.net and XMind.org domain names, the "Site") such as downloading XMind software and accessing the XMind Share service require you to have an XMind account. We ask for certain personal information when you create an XMind account, including your email address and a password, which is used to protect your account from unauthorized access. Meanwhile, your XMind ID and password will be saved through particular encryption. Any one including XMind, can not access your XMind account without your personal authorization. When you purchase our products and/or services, we also collect necessary personal information such as your contact and payment information in order to complete the transaction. 
  * Usage Information. We may record information about your usage, such as when you use the Site, the channels, groups, and favorites you subscribe to, the contacts you communicate with, the content you view, and the frequency and size of data transfers, as well as information you display or click on in the Site (including UI elements, settings, and other information). If you are logged in, we may associate that information with your account. We may use clear GIFs (a.k.a. "Web Beacons") in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients.   
We may also ask for personal information related to your use of our products and services when you contact our support staff by phone, download software updates, participate in one of our online surveys, or register product information. 
  * Content Uploaded to Site. In general, any personal information or content that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, within your profile pages, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others (collectively "Public Content"). If a "private sharing" feature is available to you and your uploaded content is enabled only for "private sharing," then XMind will exercise commercially reasonable efforts to restrict access only to the people whom you specify in your contact list for that content.
  * Data storage and transmission with XMind Cloud. Any content uploaded to XMind Cloud will be protected by XMind Ltd to the greatest extent. Industry standard encryption(SSL) is used to protect your data transmission with XMind Cloud, to avoid that your XMind files (including texts, photos, and attachments inside files) are visited, tampered, revealed or damaged during uploading or downloading without your authorization. We request the file storage service companies to strictly perform the obligations of data confidentiality. If the obligations are not well performed, they will be investigated for legal responsibility or their cooperations with XMind will be terminated.

### USES

  * If you submit personally identifiable information to us through the Site, we use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the general and personalized features and functionality of the Site, and to process any flagging activity or correspondence you send to us.
  * Your account name (not your email address) is displayed to other users of the Site when you upload content or send messages through the Site and other users can contact you through messages and comments. Any Public Content that you submit to the Site may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public.
  * We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major Site changes or for customer service purposes).
  * We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous and aggregate user usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the Site and our products, and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, analyzing, and processing user preferences and trends, as well as user activity and communications.
  * We use cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to: (a) store information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the Site; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests.

### INFORMATION THAT IS PUBLICLY AVAILABLE

  * When you create an account on the Site, some information about your account and your account activity will be provided to other users of the Site. This may include the date you opened your account, the date you last logged into your account, your age (if you choose to make it public), the country and the number of content items you have viewed.

  * Your account name (not your email address) is displayed to other users when you engage in certain activity on the Site, such as when you upload content or send messages through the Site. Other users can contact you through messages and comments.
  * You may also have some personal information that will be visible to other users on your home page(which is the public facing page for your account on the Site)[] This may include a profile picture, your name, public maps, gender, or other details.
  * If you choose to add certain features to your home page, then these features and your activity associated with these features will be displayed to other users and may be aggregated and shared with your confirmed contacts or other users. Such shared activity may include what content you favorite, what content you rated and what content you have uploaded.
  * Any Public Content that you submit to the Site may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public.

### YOUR CHOICES

  * You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information through the Site, in which case you can still view content and explore the Site, but XMind may not be able to provide certain services to you.
  * You may update or correct your personal profile information and email preferences at any time by visiting your account profile page.
  * You may control the information that is available to other users and your confirmed contacts at any time by editing your account and the features that are included on your home page.

### THIRD-PARTY ADVERTISERS, LINKS TO OTHER SITES

XMind allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the Site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the Site. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see.

XMind does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. However, please note that if an advertiser asks XMind to show an advertisement to a certain audience (for example, men ages 18-34) or audience segment (for example, men ages 18-24 who have viewed certain categories of content) and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. The advertiser may also use information regarding your use of the Site, such as the number of times you viewed an ad (but not any personally identifiable information), to determine which ads to deliver to you.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. XMind's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or websites. Any data obtained by third-party ad servers subsequently shared with XMind is maintained and dealt with by XMind in accordance with this privacy policy.

The Site may offer links to other websites. When you click on links to other websites, we encourage you to read their privacy policies. Their standards may differ from ours.

### PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES AND PROBLEM RESOLUTION

XMind, Ltd. may update its privacy policy at any time. If the ownership of all or substantially all of the XMind business, or individual business units owned by XMind Ltd., were to change, your user information may be transferred to the new owner so the service can continue operations. In any such transfer of information, your user information would remain subject to comparable promises as made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy.

If you have any comments or questions related to this privacy policy, please contact us through the ways listed below.

### CONTACT

  * Email: support@xmind.net
  * Skype: support.xmind
